your health insurance provides you and
your family Financial Security it also
provides you a tax deduction under
section 80d of Income Tax Act 1961.
[Music]
thank you
if every member of the family including
parents is under 60 years of age the
policy holder is entitled for a tax
deduction up to 50 000 rupees If the
policyholders parents are above 60 years
of age and the policy holder is under 60
years of age he is entitled for a tax
deduction up to 55 000 rupees if both
the policyholder and his parents are
above 60 years of age the policy holder
is entitled for a tax deduction up to 60
000 rupees
enjoy the financial benefits with rcici
Lombards health insurance policy
[Music]